insoft.com 2014-10-02

# Insoft.com

## Terms and Conditions

This "Privacy Policy" is part of the Terms of Use for [www.insoft.com.](http://www.insoft.com/). This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we will use the information you provide when you use this Website, as well as how we will use other information that we collect based on that use. By using the Website, you consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy covers the Website. If You have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, You should contact us at [babu@insoft.com](mailto:babu@insoft.com) at Prince Infocity, 6th Floor, No-286/1 & 286/2, Rajiv Gandhi Salai, Kandanchavadi, Chennai 600 096 (India). "Personal Information" means information that would allow a third party to contact you by learning your identity, including, for example, Your full name, address, telephone number, or email address.,

Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the ways in which we collect, use and protect your Personal Information. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you in accordance with the process described in the Terms of Use

### Disclosure of Personal Information

We do not sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties for the purposes of marketing theproducts or services. Although we may disclose aggregated information about the use of our Website, that information does not contain Personal Information. We may share Personal Information with our contractors and service providers solely for the purpose of maintaining, enhancing, or adding to the functionality of the Website. In the case of criminal investigations, including but not limited to fraud or alleged illegal activity, we may share your Personal Information with law enforcement and government authorities. As [www.insoft.com.](http://www.insoft.com/) continues to develop its business, [www.insoft.com.](http://www.insoft.com/) might sell or buy lines of business or assets. If all or substantially all of [www.insoft.com.](http://www.insoft.com/)'s business (or a line of business) or assets (or the assets of a line of [www.insoft.com.](http://www.insoft.com/) \- business) are acquired by a third party, Personal Information of [www.insoft.com.](http://www.insoft.com/) users will generally be one of the transferred business assets.

We reserve the right to include your collected Personal Information and other information we collect as described herein as an asset in any such transfer to a third party. Should you post a resume, the amount of information you choose to keep confidential is entirely up to your discretion. You may enter as much or as little information as you choose. All information posted will only be visible to recruiters of the company. In your use of the Website, We also store such information as jobs You've applied to, your resume, and similar information. We track clickstream data to monitor utilization and ensure good customer experience.

### Internet Protocol Address

Like most websites, We collect Internet Protocol ("IP") address from all visitors to the Website. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Website, analyze trends, track users' movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the Website, and deliver customized, personalized content

### Security

[]()[www.insoft.com.](http://www.insoft.com/) has implemented and follows industry standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception or processing of Personal Information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect Your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warranty the security of any such Personal Information.

### Legal Disclaimer

We may disclose Your Personal Information when required by law or in the good-faith/belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on [www.insoft.com.](http://www.insoft.com/). As such, we cannot ensure that your Personal Information will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, we may be legally obligated to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may circumvent our security measures to unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.
